# FAVOUR **NWEVO**

Koforidua, Ghana · +233 24 842 9877

favournwevo@gmail.com · favour-nwevo-055017150 (LinkedIn)

I am a full-stack web developer with 3 years of experience in creating and maintaining web applications for various industries. I have proficient knowledge of both front-end and back-end technologies, such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP(Laravel), PostgreSQL, and MySQL. I have successfully completed several projects, ranging from simple websites to complex e-commerce platforms. I am always eager to learn new skills and technologies and improve my code quality. I am looking for a challenging and rewarding role where I can apply my creativity and problem-solving skills to develop innovative web solutions that meet the needs of the clients.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

MAR 2021 - MAR 2022

#### **BACKEND DEVELOPER, ZELUS TECHNOLOGIES**

Created landing pages, dashboards and web applications using PHP Framework (Laravel) and Livewire with Alpine JS programming languages.

**NOV 2022 - JUNE 2023** 

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER, FREELANCER

Managed both back-end and front-end aspects of development process.

**JULY 2023 - PRESENT** 

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER, Rx HEALTH INFO SYSTEM

My main responsibilities were to design, develop, and test software applications for the Rx. Health platform, which is a cloud-based system that enables healthcare providers to manage patient records, monitor vital signs, and deliver personalized care plans.

### **EDUCATION**

**JUL 2019** 

**HIGHER NATIONAL DIPLOMA (HND),** KOFORIDUA TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY Eastern Region, Ghana.

**DEC 2022** 

**BSC. COMPUTER SCIENCE,** VALLEY VIEW UNIVERSITY

Greater Accra, Ghana

ì

## **SKILLS**

- Back-End and Database Skills
- Complex Problem Solving
- Avid Learner
- Responsive Web Design
- Database Development

- MVC Architecture
- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS
- Web Architecture
- Website Maintenance
- Application Development

## **LANGUAGES**

English: First Language